



+98 921 635 1266



Tehran, Iran



morteza-karimi.ir



me@morteza-karimi.ir



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi

# **Hard Skills**

| PHP          | $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$ |
|--------------|---|
| Symfony 4    |   |
| Yii2         |   |
| Ansible      |   |
| Angular      |   |
| JavaScript   |   |
| Docker       |   |
| Gitlab CI/CD | $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$     |
| Laravel      | $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$     |
| Python       | $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$     |
| Node.JS      | $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$     |
| Tensorflow   | $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$     |
| OpenCV       | $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$     |
|              |   |

### Soft Skills

- Team Work
- Decision-making
- Problem-solving
- Time management
- Adaptability
- Critical thinking

## **Interests**









# Morteza Karimi

Full-Stack Developer | DevOps Engineer

### **About Me**

I'm a flexible learner and detail-oriented individual with valuable experience in different fields such as Web Developing, Deep learning, Networking, Linux, Windows...

As a boy with teamwork character, I always work side by side with a team in all companies at which I have worked.

I extremely enjoy new experiences and challenges. In other words, I prefer to follow new challenges instead of routine works. The quote "Either try as hard as you wish or wish as hard as you try" has been always my motto.

By the way reputation for creativity, problem-solving, hard-working, and team working are the highlights of my character.

# **Experience**

#### **Bugloos**

Junior DevOps Engineer

2021 - Present

According to one of our projects that were based on Microservice architecture and our team's needs, I felt that we need more modern and new ways to develop and improve our project. So as I had basic knowledge in Docker and Ansible fields, I tried to make some automatic solutions in project architecture. I used Gitlab CI/CD to reduce the volume of repetitive daily tasks so I helped the company and project to develop it and also as a DevOps engineer I supervise on project's development and Operation.

#### **Bugloos**

Full-Stack Web developer

2020 - Present

I worked as a developer in Bugloss company but after 6 months I felt we needed more knowledge about Angular to develop the company's project faster and better than in the past. So I started to learn Angular and worked on different case studies until I mastered that and improved my job position in Bugloss from backend developer to Fullstack developer. I tried to share my knowledge with my teammates and tried to make a better structure for developing the company's project. The structure I made caused me to have a good effect to do more tasks with the best quality in less time in each release. After this good experience for myself improvement, I tried to research and work in the DevOps field so after some time I could have corporate in this field too with the Bugloos company.





+98 921 635 1266



Tehran, Iran



morteza-karimi.ir



me@morteza-karimi.ir



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi

## **Hard Skills**

**PHP** Symfony 4 Yii2 **Ansible**  $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$ **Angular JavaScript Docker** Gitlab CI/CD ••000 Laravel • • 0 0 0 • • 000 **Python** Node.JS ••000 **Tensorflow**  $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$ **OpenCV** ••000

# Soft Skills

- Team Work
- Decision-making
- Problem-solving
- Time management
- Adaptability
- Critical thinking

## Interests









### **Bugloos**

Back-End Web developer

2019 - 2020

I start my work in Bugloos as a backend developer and work on some projects with different domains some like e-commerce and portals. try to improve project calculation algorithms, improve query response time for projects, and also improve deprecated bundles and extensions. also, we try to improve workflow for projects to get more efficient releases.

### **Heyzha Programming Co**

Web Application Developer

2017 - 2019

Cooperation with Heyzha company was a great spark for success in my work life. I did lots of project in this company. At first I started my work with solving the problems of a website with Laravel framework. Also I developed other websites with Yii2 framework and it followed a great impact because it caused 33% improvement in all the projects of Heyzha company. In the same way the income of company for developing more and more projects had improved, So the company experienced an up ward trend. By the way I experienced such a great challenges in designing complicated portals.

# **Khayyam University of Mashhad**

Back-End Web developer

2014 - 2016

In Khayyam university I had a game project. Its name was tik-tak-toe that was in relation with IOS app. For developing it, I used node js platform and socket io library. Also I experience a team work project in this university. It was developing Khayyam university culture center website. Actually because of my good background in bachelor final project, use node.js and PHP together, this great project was given to me.

### **Freelance Experience**

Full-Stack Web developer

2012 - Present

• Promac Co.

For the first time I used my admin panel in developing this website, so it followed a great impact and it was the satisfaction of employer.

• Rastegary charity website

It's one of my freelance works in the early years of my work field of web de-

I tried to use PHP MVC framework Yii And UI framework Bootstrap in this web project.





+98 921 635 1266



Tehran, Iran



morteza-karimi.ir



me@morteza-karimi.ir



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi

# **Hard Skills**

**PHP** Symfony 4 Yii2 **Ansible**  $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$ **Angular JavaScript Docker** Gitlab CI/CD ••000 Laravel • • 0 0 0 • • 000 **Python** Node.JS • • 000 **Tensorflow**  $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$ **OpenCV** ••000

# **Soft Skills**

- Team Work
- Decision-making
- Problem-solving
- Time management
- Adaptability
- o Critical thinking

## Interests









The first ideas of building my custom admin module for the next projects was occurred during developing this project that was very useful for my future projects.

• Variable project

I've done different kind of student projects that included website design and android application.

I worked with electron framework, Qt C++ framework, python language and many other techniques in these projects.

# **Volunteer Experience**

# **Artificial Intelligence projects**

#### Programmer

2017 - Present

Because of my intrest in Image Processing field, voluntary I worked on image processing projects.

Also based on my information about deep learning I started working on a project, that is about forecasting financial markets which is currently underway.

### Create RTL template based on Gentelella theme

Front-End & Translate

2014 - Present

Sharing my abilities and information in translating and RTL on open source template was one of my great work experience.

By searching in google I found out a useful template so I worked on it because having good and free template could be useful for web developers.

I got familiar with different tools in this project and got many feedback from many people all around the world that helped me in developing this project.

#### Valencia fan club website in Iran

Full-Stack Web developer

201<sup>L</sup>

I started my first work experience in field of "web developing" with designing 0 to 100 Valencia fan club website. I had a serious plan for developing this website that led to my employer satisfaction. I used Yii framework for this website to create complicated system such as like, comment and ... efficiently.

#### **Web Development Teacher**

Teacher

2014 - 2019

I always like to share my information with others so I like to have some experiences in designing open source projects or teaching my information to others. So I decided to schedule and plan some courses to teach web development lessons to my students.





+98 921 635 1266



Tehran, Iran



morteza-karimi.ir



me@morteza-karimi.ir



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi

# **Hard Skills**

PHP Symfony 4 Yii2 **Ansible** Angular JavaScript **Docker** Gitlab CI/CD ••000 Laravel ••000 **Python** ••000 Node.JS • • 000 **Tensorflow** ••000

# **Soft Skills**

**OpenCV** 

- Team Work
- Decision-making
- Problem-solving
- Time management
- Adaptability
- Critical thinking

## **Interests**









••000

### Education

#### **Shahrood University of Technology**

2017 - Present

Master of Science in Artificial Intelligence; GPA: 3.77 (16.46/20)

#### Khayyam University of Mashhad

2012 - 2017

Bachelor of Engineering in Software Engineering; GPA: 3.17 (15.47/20)